(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
#ねぽらぼ1周年
#NePolabo1stAnniversary
雪花ラミィ 1周年
Yukihana Lamy 1st Anniversary
うわあああ！皆さん、こんらみーです！
Whoaaa! Hello everyone, Kon-Lamy!
ホロライブ5期生の雪花ラミィです！皆さん、こんらみー！
I'm Yukihana Lamy from Hololive Gen 5! Kon-Lamy, everyone!
地獄へようこそ！
Welcome to hell!
え、ということで、今日はですね、雪花ラミィ1周年ということで...
Well, today marks Yukihana Lamy's 1st anniversary...
...この #雪花ラミィ1周年 プラス...
...and using the #YukihanaLamy1stAnniversary tag plus...
...#ねぽらぼ1周年。こちらのタグでたくさん呟いていただければなと思います！
...#NePolabo1stAnniversary. I hope you'll tweet a lot using these tags!
え、ということでね、今日は本来であれば、お酒が飲みたかったんですよ、お酒が。
Actually, I really wanted to drink some alcohol today.
ま、ですがね、このご時世なんで、お酒は飲めないので。
But under the current circumstances, I can't drink alcohol.
ま、でもね、せっかくの1周年なので、今日はラミィが...
However, since it's a special 1st anniversary, today I...
...大好きな先輩たちを呼んで、好き勝手やりたいと思います！イェーイ！
...invited my favorite seniors to do whatever we want! Yay!
え、ということでね、ちょっと先輩... あ、なんかちょっと一人丸見えの人もいるし。
So, about the seniors... Oh, wait, I can see one of them clearly already.
先... あ、アキ先輩！
Sen... Oh, Aki-senpai!
あ、ちょっと牛すじ追加でお願いします。
Ah, can I get another order of beef tendon, please?
ここ居酒屋じゃないんですけど。アキ先輩、違う！
This isn't an izakaya, you know! Aki-senpai, no!
牛すじとかないんで。
We don't have beef tendon here.
あ、ちょっと人の家の日本酒勝手に飲むのは... あ、なんか呟... いらっしゃいませ！
Hey, don't just drink my sake without asking... Oh, someone's... Welcome!
牛すじお待たせしました！
Your beef tendon is ready!
うわ、うまい、これこれ！
Whoa, delicious! This is it!
待って、1周年！待って、牛すじ！団長も食べる！団長も食べる！
Wait, the anniversary! Wait, beef tendon! Danchou wants to eat too!
テーブルを... テーブルにめり込んでるから。いいの？牛すじ食べていいんですか？
The table... You're literally stuck in the table. Is it okay? Can I eat the beef tendon?
どっしょテーブル破壊しながら入ってこないでください！
Please don't come in while destroying the table!
ごめんね、ごめんね、ごめんね！
Sorry, sorry, sorry!
ラミィ、お誕生日... じゃない。1周年おめでとう！
Lamy, happy birthday... No, happy 1st anniversary!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
真ん中に、真ん中に。ありがとうございます、真ん中。
To the middle, to the middle. Thank you, I'll take the middle.
え、じゃ、え、ちょっと誰かな誰かなっていうか、自己紹介をしてもらってもよろしいでしょうか？
Well then, could you all introduce yourselves now?
じゃあ、まあ一番ね、先輩なところからいかせていただきましょうか。
Let's start with the most senior member.
お願いします！
Please go ahead!
ホロライブ1期生の癒し系ハーフエルフ、アキロゼことアキ・ローゼンタールです！
I'm the soothing half-elf of Hololive Gen 1, Aki Rosenthal, also known as Akirose!
今日は...
Today...
酒仲間のね、ラミィちゃんを...
Lamy, my drinking buddy...
...お祝いしに来たので、いっぱい遊びたいと思います！
...I came to celebrate, so I want to play a lot!
イェーイ！
Yay!
飲んでください！
Please drink!
次は誰？誰？誰いく？
Who's next? Who? Who's going?
はい！皆さん、こんまっする！
Yes! Hello, everyone, Kon-muscle!
ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエルです。
I'm Shirogane Noel from Hololive Gen 3.
さっきはちょっとラミィの綺麗な白い手袋をはがいして...
Earlier, I was peeling off Lamy's white gloves...
踏みしめてきたんですけど...
...and stepping on them, but...
踏みしめてきたね。
You did step on them.
今日はね、本当ラミィもう1年経つんだ。
Today, really, it's already been a year for Lamy.
そうなんです。早いな。
That's right. It's fast.
な、ちょっと今日は全力で楽しい配信にしていきます！
So today I'm going all out for a fun stream!
イェーイ！
Yay!
動きが... 動きが独特だね。
Your movements... your movements are unique.
自己紹介しようかな？
Should I introduce myself?
皆さん、じゃあ一緒にポーズ決めてください。
Everyone, let's strike a pose together.
えっと、何だっけ？
Um, what was it again?
あー、はーい！
Ah, yes!
ホロライブ... ホロライブ...
Hololive... Hololive...
ちょっと待って、やばい。イヤホン取れた。
Wait a sec, oh no. My earphone came off.
えっと、何だっけ？
Um, what was it?
思い出して！
Remember!
宝鐘マリン、思い出して！宝鐘海賊団船長の...
Marine, remember! The captain of the Pirates...
...宝鐘マリンです！
...is Houshou Marine!
ちょっと足が...
Wait, my leg...
決まったー！
That's it!
はい！ということでね、今日は地獄の幕開けということで。
Yes! So, today marks the start of hell.
いや、マリンさんふざけないでくださいよ。ちょっと。
Hey, Marine-san, don't mess around. Honestly.
めっちゃ疲れた、今。もうすでに疲れたけども。
I'm so tired now. I'm already tired, but...
でもあの、机の下に入るので、もうすでにお疲れ様。
But, I'm already exhausted from the table crawling.
かくれんぼから始まりましたけれども。
It all started with hide-and-seek.
今日、皆さん、来てくれてありがとうございます。
Thank you everyone for coming today.
ありがとうございます。来ましたよ。
Thank you. We're here.
ね、本来はここで、お酒を飲みたいわけなんですけれども。
Normally I'd want to have a drink here, but...
今日はね、お酒が飲めない分、ラミィがしたいことを
Since we can't drink today, I'll do what I want
先輩たちと一緒にいろいろやっていこうと思います！
with my seniors instead!
ヤッホー！やったー！
Yahoo! Yay!
えっ、ちょっと、すでに息切れが。
Wait, I'm already out of breath.
深呼吸して、深呼吸して。
Take a deep breath, deep breath.
ということで、早速ではありますが、
So, without further ado,
お、実は今日ラミィ1周年ということで、
actually, since today is Lamy's 1st anniversary,
え、先輩たちにですね、
I asked my seniors
プレゼントを欲しいな、なんておねだりしちゃったんですけど。
for presents as a little favor.
え、持ってきた？プレゼント。
Wait, did you bring it? The present.
え、知らない。え、持ってきてないよ。
Eh, I don't know. Eh, I didn't bring anything.
いやいや、持ってないとかコーナー進まない。
No way, if you don't have them, we can't progress.
えー、いや、ないんだけど。ない、ない。
Wait, really, we don't have them. No, no.
プレゼント、ないよ。ないよ、ラミィちゃん。
There are no presents. None, Lamy-chan.
次のコーナー行きますか？
Shall we move to the next corner?
持ってきた、持ってきた。持ってきましたよ。
We brought them, we brought them. We brought them!
ということで今回プレゼント持ってきていただいたので、
Since you all brought presents this time,
そのままもらうだけじゃ面白くないので、
it's not fun just receiving them directly,
ちょっとね、ゲームをしたいと思います！
so I'd like to play a game instead!
題して、
Titled,
プレゼントで「箱の中身は何だろうな」！
"What's in the Box" with presents!
なんだろうな、なんだろうな。
What is it, what is it?
ちょっと、待って、息切れが。
Wait, I'm out of breath.
まださ、10分も経ってないんだけど。始まったばっかだぞ。
It's not even been 10 minutes yet. We just started.
これからプレゼントが入った箱が運ばれてきます。
A box containing the presents will be brought in.
ラミィは中身を見ずにそれを触って当てたいと思います。
Lamy will touch it without looking and try to guess.
当てられなかった場合、プレゼントは没収となるらしいです。
If I can't guess, the present will be confiscated.
あら。何で自分からそんな枷を... 地獄へと行ってしまう。
Oh. Why impose such a hurdle... walking into hell.
絶対当てる自信がある、っていう感じね。
You seem really confident you'll guess it.
それでは、スタッフさん、箱の準備をお願いします。
Now then, staff, please prepare the box.
お、来た。すごい。あら、何か卑猥な。
Oh, it's here. Amazing. Oh, something lewd.
何ですか、この卑猥なモザイクは。
What's with this lewd mosaic?
モザイク全部卑猥じゃないから。
Not all mosaics are lewd.
ちょっと待って、マリンとラミィここ立って、真ん中。
Wait, Marine and Lamy stand here, in the middle.
これ、昨日見たあの出航してるシオン船長の...
Is this Captain Shion setting sail that I saw...
ラミィ、しない、しない。しないの？
Lamy, don't do it. You're not doing it?
よかった、よかった。何だろう、このモザイク。
Good, good. What is this mosaic?
ここにね、プレゼントが入るわけなんですけれども。
This is where the presents will go.
ラミィは目をつむりますんで、中身をお見せします。
Lamy will close her eyes, so I'll show the contents.
はい！じゃあちょっと、どなたから？
Yes! So, who's first?
じゃあ、最初はアキロゼのものから行こうかな。
Well, shall we start with Aki Rosenthal's first?
何だろう。ラミィが当てれるようにアシストしようかな。
What is it? I'll give Lamy a bit of an assist.
お願いします。そうですね。
Please do. Right.
画面にもみんなの出るのかな？
Will it appear on screen for everyone?
ラミィは今目つむってるんでわかんないんですけど。
Lamy's eyes are closed so I don't know.
それでは、最初のプレゼント。ドン！
Now then, the first present. Bam!
こちらやっぱりすごく悩んだんですよ。もうめちゃくちゃ。
I really struggled with this one. A lot.
いろいろ考えて、ここに最終的に至りました。
I thought about it and finally arrived at this.
思考の経路教えてもらっても...
Tell us your train of thought...
あんまり言っちゃうとね、ヒントになっちゃうから。
If I say too much, it'll be a total hint.
とりあえず触ってみてほしいなと思いますので。
For now, I'd like you to try touching it.
よーい...
Ready...
怖っ...
Scary...
スタート！
Start!
あ、怖怖怖怖！
Ah, scary, scary, scary, scary!
どこ？
Where?
あーっ！何これ？！
Ah! What is this?!
いや、刺さったね今。
Wow, it poked you just now.
刺さってる、刺さってる。
It's poking, it's poking.
先っぽが刺さった。
The tip poked you.
あ、先っぽなんかね...
Ah, the tip is somehow...
つまんで...ラミィが先っぽクリクリしてますけども。
Pinching... Lamy is twirling the tip, though.
なんか言い方がちょっとドゥフｗ
The way you said it is a bit... (laughs)
何これ？！
What is this?!
間違ってない？
Is that right?
触り...今あの先端が尖ってるんですけど。
Touching... Now, that tip is pointed.
そうですね。先端が尖ってて...
That's right. The tip is pointed and...
もっと味わってて。
Savor it more.
もっとよく触って。
Touch it more thoroughly.
なんか丸...
Something round...
もっと触って撫で回して。
Touch it more, stroke it all over.
両手で！
With both hands!
分かったこれ！分かった！
I know this! I know!
え、本当に？もう分かっちゃった？
Eh, really? You already figured it out?
大丈夫？
Are you sure?
え、これあれですよね？あの...ちょっと匂いがするやつ。
Eh, this is that, right? Um... the one that smells a bit.
あー...まぁそうとも限らない...
Ah... well, that might not necessarily be the case...
すごいもう...
Amazing...
そうとは...ほう...
Not necessarily... oh...
どうかな？
I wonder?
え、これもうえラミィこれちょっといい？大丈夫？これいける？
Eh, this already... Lamy, is this okay? Are you sure? You got this?
あ、いけますか？
Ah, you're ready?
じゃあラミィちゃん答えまね...
Then Lamy-chan, guess...
ちょっと違うねｗ
That's a bit different. (laughs)
はい、じゃあそこまで。一旦ストップで。
Alright, that's it. Stop for now.
はい。
Yes.
それでは正解をお願いします。
Now, please give the answer.
え、これはニンニク！ニンニクです！
Eh, this is garlic! It's garlic!
正解！
Correct!
なんで分かった？
How did you know?
え、なんかね先端が尖ってて...下にいくにつれてこうモコモコしてる。
Well, the tip was pointed... and it gets bumpy as you go down.
あぁなるほどね。手触りで。
Ah, I see. By how it felt.
いや待って、その前にアキロゼ先輩はなんでさ、これを？どういう思考のプロセスがあってここに？
Wait, before that, Aki-rose senpai, why this? What was your thought process to end up here?
どういうこと？なんでこれをあげようと思った？
What do you mean? Why did you think of giving this?
あ、じゃあちょっと語らせていただきますね。
Ah, let me explain then.
最初お酒で、いろんなお酒持ってこうと思ったんだけど...
At first I thought of bringing various alcohols, but...
...まぁ雪民たちからも各種プレゼントをもらったしと思って。
...I thought she already got various presents from the Yukimin.
まぁ確かに。
That's true.
そうそう。で、じゃあおつまみにしようと思ってスルメイカにしようと思ったんだけど...
Right. So I thought I'd get some snacks and considered dried squid, but...
...ちょっと匂ったりとか持って帰るのにね、支障出ちゃうかなと思って。
...I thought it might smell or be a hassle to take home.
あぁ。
Ah.
考えて考えて、あ、飲みすぎのラミィちゃんと健康になってもらいたいから！
I thought and thought, and since Lamy-chan drinks too much, I want her to be healthy!
だからって生をボンっていうのは...
But just because of that, giving it raw like "boom"...
え、これでね是非お酒に合うガーリック料理配信してほしいなと。
Eh, with this, I definitely want you to do a garlic cooking stream that goes well with alcohol.
あ、いい！なるほど！奥に。アキロゼ先輩のニンニクでね。
Ah, nice! I see! Deeply. With Aki-rose senpai's garlic.
さぁアキロゼのニンニクで。ありがとうございました。
Alright, with Aki-rose's garlic. Thank you very much.
かじりながらね帰ってください。
Please go home while nibbling on it.
かじりながらは帰らないけれども。生で。
I won't go home nibbling on it. Raw.
はい、ありがとうございます。これはね頂いていきたいと思います。
Yes, thank you very much. I'll take this.
素晴らしいですね。イェイ！
That's wonderful. Yay!
え、それではね、続いて...ちょっとまたラミィは目を閉じたいと思いますが。
Well then, moving on... I'm going to close my eyes again.
え、次はどなたの先輩のプレゼント？
Um, whose senpai's present is next?
はい、次はじゃあ団長が行きたいと思います！
Yes, then it's Danchou's turn next!
お、お願いします。
Oh, please go ahead.
何だろうな？じゃあラミィ目つぶってもらって。
I wonder what it is? Then I'll close my eyes.
あ、お願いします。行きますね。
Ah, please do. Here I go.
なるほど。え、団長はこんな感じになっております。
I see. Eh, Danchou's is like this.
な、いいじゃんいいじゃん！
Wow, looks good!
いいでしょう。これはね...何か理由があるんだけどそれは後から述べたいと思いますので。
It's nice, right. There's a reason for this, but I'll explain it later.
よろしく。
Look forward to it.
これ難しいんじゃないの？
Isn't this difficult?
難しいよね。
It's difficult, right.
ま、ちょっとじゃあ行きますか？
Well, shall we start then?
はい！はい！では、スタート！
Yes! Yes! Then, start!
どこだろうな？
Where is it?
どこかな？
I wonder where?
あ、お、触れました。何か触れて...
Ah, oh, I touched it. I'm touching something...
何これ？！
What is this?!
結構大胆に触ってるね。
You're touching it quite boldly.
結構両手で行くんだ。
Going in with both hands.
あ、えちょっと待って...何これ？！真ん中！
Ah, eh wait... What is this?! The middle!
落ちた！落ちた！落ちちゃった！団長のプレゼント！
It fell! It fell! It fell off! Danchou's present!
怒り方ｗ
The way she's getting angry (laughs)
落ちちゃった、落ちちゃった！なんか真ん中...あれ？
It fell off, it fell off! Something in the middle... huh?
今２個にセパレートしましたね。
It just separated into two.
セパレートになりましたね。
It separated.
パーツが外れました。
A part came off.
え、何これ？なんか独特の手触りが...
Eh what is this? It has a unique feel...
あぁ！お！でも！あぁ！でも察し...あぁこれは...触り方、いいよいいよ。
Ah! Oh! But! Ah! But the guess... Ah this... the way you're touching it is good, good.
今先っぽを楽しんでる所ですね。
She's enjoying the tip right now.
正しい使い方してる。
She's using it correctly.
先っぽがね、すごく気持ちいいやつだからこれ。
Because the tip feels really good.
お、これ！
Oh, this!
あの、はい。まぁ興奮しないで。
Um, yes. Well, don't get excited.
ごめんなさい。
Sorry.
分かった。
I got it.
お、お！はい、分かりましたか？いいですね。
Oh, oh! Yes, did you figure it out? Nice.
ではここで...ストップ！
Then, right here... stop!
はい、それではラミィさん答えを言ってもらってもいいですか？
Yes, then Lamy-san, could you tell us the answer?
これは...メイクブラシ！
This is... a makeup brush!
正解！
Correct!
すごい！よく分かった！
Amazing! You knew it well!
途中で土台からパカッて外れたからなかなか難しいかと思ったけど。
I thought it would be quite difficult because it snapped off from the base halfway through.
あぁ、もうこれでもやっぱりね触ってて...馴染みがね？
Ah, well, I guess after touching it... the familiarity?
そうそうそう。結構いつも使ってるっていうのもあって分かりやすかったです。
Yeah yeah yeah. I use it quite often, so it was easy to tell.
あぁなるほどね。ちょっとねこれを選んだ理由っていうのも...
Ah, I see. And the reason for choosing this...
はいはい。まぁ多分ねこのアキロゼ先輩とかまぁマリンだと...
Yes, yes. Well, probably with Aki-rose senpai or Marine...
...なんかとんでもない奇抜なのが来るなとラミィも先っぴーって予想ついてて。
...Lamy probably anticipated that something incredibly bizarre would come.
読まれてたねｗ
We were read. (laughs)
で、なんかこの前そのラミィとASMRした時に、そうジェルボールは託したんだけど...
And, when I did ASMR with Lamy the other day, I entrusted the gel balls to her, but...
...団長ねこのブラシで、あのもう１個あるんだけど、もう１個もプレゼントするんだけど...
...Danchou has this brush, and there's another one too, I'll give both as a present...
...両耳でサワサワってするとすごくいい音がするから是非是非ね。
...if you do it in both ears, it makes a really good sound, so please do it.
あぁ、流石音！
Ah, as expected of sound!
ありがとうございます。これはねじゃあちょっと今度のASMR配信で。
Thank you very much. I'll use this in my next ASMR stream.
使ってください。
Please use it.
いいね、癒される。お耳をサワサワしたいと...
Nice, it's healing. I want to stroke the ears...
思います。
I think so too.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
いいプレゼント！
What a nice gift!
素晴らしい！
Wonderful!
よかった！
I'm glad!
それじゃあ最後は団長じゃなくて船長のね...
Now, the final one isn't from Danchou, but from Senchou...
はい、船長のね、プレゼントをね、
Yes, Senchou's gift.
じゃあちょっと準備したいと思います。ラミィ、目閉じて。
I'll get it ready. Lamy, close your eyes.
はい、目閉じます。
Okay, eyes closed.
いやこれはね、まあ理由はね、後で説明しようと思うんですけども、
I'll explain the reason later,
これぜひね、ラミィに、えー何ですか、使ってほしいなと思って。
but I really want Lamy to use this.
使ってほしい！
Use it!
ヒントになってるかも、中身は。フワフワになっております。
The contents might be a hint. It's fluffy.
というわけで、皆さんにお見せしたいと思います。こちらです！
So, I'll show everyone. Here it is!
え？
Eh?
ジャジャジャンと。
Ta-da!
あ、見せないんだった。
Oh, I wasn't supposed to show it.
これは見せません。
I won't show this.
見せないの！？
You're not showing it!?
見せないんか！
You won't show it?!
そうだそうだ、忘れてた。はい、見せません。
Right, right, I forgot. Yes, I won't show it.
じゃあラミィ見せないのでね、リスナーの皆さんも何が出てくるのか考えてみてください。
I won't show Lamy, so listeners, please guess what it is.
じゃあラミィ、早速触ってどうぞ。では、スタート！
Now Lamy, go ahead and touch it. Ready, start!
はい。
Okay.
え、それ大丈夫？動かない？
Wait, is it okay? It doesn't move?
やめてよ！
Stop it!
あー！やだ！
Ah! No!
やめてよ！
Stop it!
あー！やめてよ！
Ah! Stop it!
何これ？何これ？何これ？何これ？
What is this? What is this? What is this?
ラミィ、何？何？実況して、実況して。
Lamy, what is it? Give us a report.
なんか...フサフサしてる。
It's... fluffy.
うん、フサフサしてる。
Yeah, it's fluffy.
フサフサしてて、紐みたいなのもついてる。
It's fluffy and has something like a string.
はいはい。
I see, I see.
え、何これ？あ、わかった！
Wait, what is this? Oh, I know!
あ、なんか音がする。
Oh, it's making a sound.
これさ...
This is...
あ！
Ah!
チャリンチャリン、リンリンしてる。
It's jingling.
もう、これね、多分...
I bet this is...
何だと思う？
What do you think?
これね、あれじゃない？
This is that, isn't it?
うん。
Yeah.
あのラミィがいつも付けてるやつじゃない？
The one Lamy always wears?
お！おお！
Oh! Ohhh!
これは大ヒント。これリスナーさんも察してきたかな？
That's a huge hint. Listeners probably realize it too.
もうちょっとじゃあ、ラミィ分かったならリスナーさんに向けてのヒントを。
Lamy, if you know, give another hint for the listeners.
これはね、ラミィが...
This is something Lamy...
えっとね、あのお正月衣装の時に...
Um, with the New Year's outfit...
お！
Oh!
おっと！
Oops!
付けたり付けてなかったりしてる...
sometimes wears and sometimes doesn't...
お、お！
Oh, oh!
あれや！
That's the one!
これは完全に理解してるまである。
She totally gets it.
おー！これいい！
Oh! This is good!
え、そうでしょう？
Right?
言ってもいいですか？これ。
Can I say what it is?
あ、言ってもいいかな？
Oh, can I say it?
終了！
Time's up!
はい、じゃあ終了ということで。じゃあラミィ、こちら何ですか？
Alright, time's up. Lamy, what is this?
猫耳！
Cat ears!
正解！
Correct!
これをラミィ、じゃあ早速ね、これ使ってほしいなと思ってるんで、付けてみてもらえませんか？
I wanted you to use these, Lamy, so could you put them on?
そうね。
Right.
え、これ付けられるんですか？
Wait, can I put them on?
付けてください！
Please do!
やっぱりね、付けてる姿がね、見たくて買ってきたので。
I bought them because I wanted to see you wearing them.
じゃあちょっとね。
Okay then.
ラミィに猫耳を...うん。
Lamy with cat ears... yeah.
はい、ポン！
Okay, ta-da!
おおー！可愛い！
Ohhh! So cute!
可愛いー！
So cute!
可愛い！
Cute!
え、すごい！
Wow, amazing!
猫耳です。
Cat ears.
じゃあちょっと、ラミィにゃんのアップを。
Let's get a close-up of Lamy-nyan.
ね、アップアップアップ。
Yeah, zoom in, zoom in.
せっかくなんで。どうかな？
Since we're here. How is it?
どうかな？ちょっとカメラ、カメラを。
How is it? Camera, camera.
あの、ラミィにゃんのアップください！ラミィの...
A close-up of Lamy-nyan, please!
ラミィの卑猥なモザイク写さないで！
Don't show Lamy's indecent mosaic!
ほら！あ！
Look! Ah!
あ、可愛いー！
Ah, so cute!
いや可愛い！ちょっとラミィこれ今日ずっと付けて。
So cute! Lamy, wear these for the rest of today.
え？ずっと付けてるの？
Eh? Wear them the whole time?
このままいこうかなって。
Let's go like this.
はい。えーありがとうございます！
Yes. Thank you very much!
え、じゃあ今回ね、ちょっとラミィとマリンの勘冴え渡りすぎて...
Well, Lamy and Marine were too sharp this time...
冴え渡りすぎたね。
Too sharp indeed.
ちょ、お前、外せよお前！
Hey you, take that off!
確かに。ちょ空気読めなくてすみません。
True. Sorry for not reading the room.
本気出しちゃった。
I was serious about it.
本気出しちゃったわ。
I really went all out.
プレゼント欲しさにね本気出しちゃったんで。あの、全問正解ということで。
I went all out for the gifts. So, I got them all right.
はい。全てお持ち帰りしたいと思います！
Yes. I'll take them all home!
うーい！よかった！でもなんかすごいさ...
Yay! I'm glad! But it's kinda...
今更なんだけど、なんかニンニクとか選んで、どうしようって今思ってるんだけど大丈夫かな？
Now that it's over, I'm wondering if picking garlic was a good idea. Is it okay?
いやもうニンニクもね、かじりながら、耳もね付けながら、耳をこうフサフサフサフサしながら帰ろうと思います。
I'll go home munching on the garlic while wearing these fluffy ears.
変態すぎる！ご変態すぎる！
Too weird! You're way too weird!
やばいね、これ。
That's crazy.
ありがとうございます！以上、「プレゼントで箱の中身は何だろうな」でしたー！
Thank you! That's the end of "What's in the gift box"!
うー！
Woo!
いやこれね、すごい。
This is really cool.
すごい！可愛いー！
Amazing! So cute!
猫耳、あ、よしよし。団長が大歓喜だよ、これ。
Cat ears, there there. Danchou is overjoyed.
これ今後、色がね変わるらしくて、今後色んなホロメンに装着できるそうですよ。
Apparently the color will change, and other Holo-members can wear them in the future.
えー！
Eh?!
すごい！活用していただきたいと思います！
Amazing! Please make good use of them!
やっぱりすげーな、そんなのなかった。
That's impressive, there was nothing like that before.
天才！天才！
Genius! Genius!
褒められてる...なんか。
Getting praised... somehow.
動きがね、ちょっと昭和入ってるけど。
The movements are a bit old-fashioned, though.
はい、ということでプレゼントもらってテンション上がってきたので、まだまだ先輩たちにはラミィのやりたいことに付き合っていただきます！
Alright, I'm in high spirits after the gifts, so my seniors will be joining me for more things I want to do!
やだー！
No way!
いやいや、もう終わっちゃうから。ちょっとすみません。
Wait, wait, it's gonna end. Excuse me.
次はですね、先輩たちが体を動かす企画！
Next up is a physical activity project for my seniors!
体動かすのね、マリン先輩もやってたんで、ラミィもねやってみたいと。
Marine-senpai did a physical activity one too, so I wanted to try it.
なるほどね。
I see.
思いまして、企画しました！えー、先輩たちと一緒に体を動かしたい...
So I planned this! I want to move my body with my seniors...
歩数計フリフリ！
Pedometer Shake!
うー！フリフリ！
Woo! Shake, shake!
だるすぎる...もう疲れてきた。
This is too much... I'm already tired.
考えただけで、ちょっと...まだ、まだ、まだ。
Just thinking about it... Wait, wait, wait.
不穏な、不穏な。
This is ominous.
えー、このコーナーではね、体のどこかに歩数計を...
In this corner, we'll put a pedometer somewhere on our bodies...
装着して、30秒間全力でフリフリしていただきます。
Equip it and shake it for 30 seconds with all your might.
なるほど。
I see.
その回数が一番多かった人が勝ちというシンプル・イズ・ベストなゲームになっております。
The person with the most shakes wins. It's a 'simple is best' kind of game.
なるほど。おー！
I see. Oh!
あの、なんか気合が！アキロゼ先輩、なんか自信ありげじゃないですか。
Oh, you're fired up! Akirose-senpai, you look quite confident.
そうそう。やっぱりね、なんかちょっとね、腰を振ることに関してはね。
Right, right. After all, you know, when it comes to shaking my hips...
そうだ、アキロゼ先輩は腰を振ることに関して他の追随を許さない。
That's right, Akirose-senpai's hip-shaking is second to none.
勝っちゃうかもしれないな。
I might just win this.
おやおやおや、でも船長もお尻ぷりぷりで生きてきてるんで。
Oh? But Sencho has also lived her life with a bouncy butt.
団長さんはどこに付けますか？
Danchou, where will you attach yours?
え、でもやっぱり力こぶあるからここかな。
Hmm, maybe here since I have muscles?
ちょっとジャンプしてみて。ジャンプしてみて。
Try jumping a bit. Jump.
一番揺れるのどこかな。自分でも答えてみない？どこ？
I wonder where shakes the most. Why don't you answer for yourself? Where?
大胸筋かな？
Maybe my pectorals?
そうですね。
I thought so.
ということで、アキ先輩が腰、マリン先輩がお尻、ノエル先輩が大胸筋ということで、はい。
So, Aki-senpai is the waist, Marine-senpai is the butt, and Noel-senpai is the pectorals.
え、もう、え、それはね、フリフリしてくれるってことですか？
Eh, wait, does that mean you're going to shake them for us?
ま、そういう...
Well, something like that...
全力で！いいんですか？ありがとうございます。
With all your might! Is that okay? Thank you so much.
秘蔵映像になっちゃうんじゃないかな。
This might become rare footage.
大丈夫かな、YouTube大丈夫かな。エロライブ帰ってきた。
Is this okay for YouTube? Ero-Live is back.
一番最初にチャレンジは誰がしてきますか？一番自信がある人。
Who's going to challenge first? Whoever is most confident.
お！アキ先輩！さすが！
Oh! Aki-senpai! As expected!
さあ、どこに。あ、もししかして...
Now, where should I put it? Oh, maybe...
ラミィちゃんが付けてくれると。ラミィ特製おねだり。
Lamy-chan will attach it for me. Lamy's special request.
付けたいだけだろ、自分。
You just want to attach it yourself, don't you?
え、どこがいいかな。
Hmm, where should I put it?
じゃあ、この辺。
Then, around here.
この辺ということで。はい。
Alright, around here then.
じゃあ、ちょっと一度ゼロカウントにして。
Let me reset it to zero first.
それではね、今腰にこの辺り、ちょうど素敵なこの辺りに付いてます。
So, it's now attached to her waist, right around this lovely spot.
じゃあ、それでは30秒間行きますよ。歩数計フリフリスタート！
Alright, here we go for 30 seconds. Pedometer shake, start!
速い！速い速い！
Fast! So fast!
激しい！
Intense!
すごいすごい！
Amazing, amazing!
アキ先輩めっちゃ速い！すごい踊ってる！
Aki-senpai is so fast! She's totally dancing!
ブルブルブル！
Shake shake shake!
ナイス、ナイスな腰です。美しすぎ！
Nice, nice hips. So beautiful!
すごい！すごい！
Amazing! Amazing!
あとどうなってんの、この揺れ！
How is she even shaking like that?!
残り10秒！9、8、7、6、5、4、3、2、1...
10 seconds left! 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1...
終了！
Finish!
なんだこれ。すごいマジで。
What was that? Seriously amazing.
結構30秒長かった。お、すごい。
30 seconds was quite long. Oh, amazing.
いくつ？131！すごーい！
How many? 131! Amazing!
すげー！これちょっと大記録じゃない？ちょっと。
Incredible! Isn't this a huge record?
動きのキレ半端なかったぞ。
Her movements were so sharp.
ダンスもしてたもんね、こうね。すごかった。
She was even dancing, like this. It was amazing.
これ勝てるかな？やばい。
Can I beat this? This is bad.
マリン先輩、これお尻で勝てるかどうか。
Marine-senpai, I wonder if you can win with your butt.
船長は、やっぱね、あの下のね、この下尻が揺れるからね。
For Sencho, you know, the lower part here, the lower butt shakes a lot.
このお尻の下の、お尻下、お尻下。ここ、ここ霜降りに。
Under the butt, lower butt... Here, on the marbling part.
マリンの霜振りに。この辺、霜降りが。
On Marine's marbling. Around here, the marbling.
ビシビシじゃない。ないよ、ビシビシ。
It's not firm at all. Not firm.
ちょっと弾け方おかしいでしょ。これ絶対お尻の穴の...
Wait, the way it's bouncing is weird. This is definitely like an anus...
確かに。すごい、どうなってるの。
True. Amazing, what's going on?
違う違う、お尻の穴になってる、これ。先輩！
No no, it's becoming an anus, this. Senpai!
ラミィそんなお尻をさ。お尻をそんな触って。ちょっとエッチだったね。
Lamy, touching my butt like that... Touching my butt so much. That was a bit lewd.
ラミィ、もしかして触りたいだけなんじゃないの？
Lamy, maybe you just want to touch it?
違う、そんなわけあるかい。
No way, that's not it.
ね、こんな絵面大丈夫？ラミィ。大丈夫じゃないじゃない。
Is this visual okay, Lamy? It's really not, is it?
何この絵面。ということで、ちょっとビシビシついでに叩くな。叩きたいだけだろ。
What is this scene? Anyway, don't slap it so hard while you're at it. You just want to slap it, don't you?
それではね、次はマリン先輩のお尻でチャレンジお願いします。
Alright, next is Marine-senpai's butt challenge.
それでは行きますよ。歩数計フリフリスタート！
Alright, here we go. Pedometer shake, start!
速い！速い！
Fast! Fast!
ガチじゃん！すごいすごい！
She's serious! Amazing, amazing!
お尻が揺れてる！頑張れ！
Her butt is shaking! Go for it!
食べたお菓子を消化するんだ！そうだ！
Digest the sweets you ate! Right!
頑張れ、頑張れ、まだ半分！まだ半分終わってない！
Go, go, still half left! Not even halfway yet!
頑張れ、顔が。真剣！あー、止めるなよ！
Go for it! Your face... so serious! Ah, don't stop!
9、8、7、6、ガンバ！4、3、2、1...
9, 8, 7, 6, do your best! 4, 3, 2, 1...
終了！
Finish!
でもすごかったよね。激しかった。
But that was amazing. So intense.
なんか小刻みっていうよりも、マリン、動きが大きかったね。
Rather than small movements, Marine, your movements were big.
疲れた。
I'm tired.
何回ですか？ちょっとね。
How many? Let's see.
マリン先輩のお尻、106回です。
Marine-senpai's butt... 106 times.
救世主（メシア）じゃなかったー！
Ah! It wasn't the Messiah!
ふーっ、まだまだだね。
Phew, still a long way to go.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
お邪魔しました。すごい汗かいた。
Sorry for the intrusion. I broke quite a sweat.
お疲れラミィ。
Good job, Lamy.
めちゃくちゃ汗かいた。ちょっと待ってね。
I really broke a sweat. Hold on a second.
ラミィ剥がして。
Lamy, peel them off.
はい。
Okay.
やべ、この後するのか。
Oh man, am I doing this next?
何、お水も飲んで。もらって。
Here, drink some water. Have some.
ああー、はい。
Ah, yes.
あつい。
Hot.
それでは。
Well then.
え、行けますか？
Eh, are you ready?
せーの、うらみこ。貼っていいです。今。
Ready, set, Uramiko. You can stick them on now.
一番揺れてるとこそうだもんな。はあーじゃないか。
That's where it shakes most. It's not like "Haa~".
あ、どっち、どっち大胸筋がいいとかありますか？
Ah, which, which pectoral muscle do you prefer?
えっとね、甲冑がない方がいいな。
Um, the one without armor would be better.
甲冑がない... だからこっちか。ここ。
Without armor... so this side? Here.
あ、より揺れそうだね。ここ。
Ah, that looks like it'll shake more. Here.
いいですか？
Is this okay?
失礼します。いいですね。
Excuse me. This is good.
ちょうどベルトのところに付けていただきありがとうございます。
Thank you for attaching it right at the belt.
え、それでは。
Eh, well then.
マリン、大丈夫？
Marine, you okay?
大丈夫、大丈夫。
I'm fine, I'm fine.
マリンが死に掛けて。
Marine is dying.
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
ソファーで休むか。はい、はい。
Should you rest on the sofa? Yes, yes.
大丈夫、大丈夫。それでは。
I'm fine, I'm fine. Well then.
えー、ノエル先輩の大胸筋チャレンジ！
Next, Noel-senpai's Pectoral Muscle Challenge!
おー。歩数計振り振り！
Oh. Pedometer shaking!
よーい、スタート！
Ready, Start!
圧の、圧の！
The pressure, the pressure!
お願いします！
Go for it!
あーいいですね。
Ah, this is good.
あー助かる、助かる。
Ah, that helps, that helps.
やばい、圧がすごい。
No way, the pressure is amazing.
それがエロライブ。
This is Erolive.
頑張れ、頑張れ！
Go for it, go for it!
ねえどんな、ねえ、ねえ。
Hey, what kind of, hey, hey.
４！３！絵面やばい。
Four! Three! The visuals are crazy.
１！終了ー！
One! Finish!
やーエロライブ感出てきた。
Yeah, that felt like Erolive.
大満足でしたね。
That was very satisfying.
いやー大満足だったみんな。
Man, everyone was very satisfied.
よかった。
Good.
今日はもう、帰ってお酒飲んで寝ようか。
Today, I'll just go home, drink some sake, and sleep.
帰りたい。
I want to go home.
今日の一番の目玉終わったな。
Today's main highlight is over.
いやいやそんなことはない。
No, no, that's not true.
ちょっと待って、動かない。ほら、ほら。
Wait a second, it's not moving. Look, look.
そうだ。回数を、おおー！
That's right. The count is, ohhh!
これなんと、なんと。
This, what, what!
１５０回！
150 times!
おおー。残念。
Ohhh. Too bad.
これは最高記録！
This is the top record!
暴力的までだね、このおっぱいに誰も適わないんだ。
It's almost violent. No one can compete with these boobs.
適わない。何これ、何これ。
Can't compete. What is this, what is this.
喜びの表し方、奇抜か？
Your way of showing joy, is it eccentric?
そんな動き初めて見たけど。
I've never seen such movements before.
初めて見た。
First time seeing it.
え、じゃあこれ剥がすのラミィがいいですか？
Eh, then, for peeling this off, should Lamy do it?
あ、どうぞ、どうぞ。
Ah, please, go ahead.
あ、でも船長が。
Ah, but Senchou...
いえいえ。あーラミィ、こっち側から。
No, no. Ah, Lamy, from this side.
もみ、もみ。
Squeeze, squeeze.
ちょっと待って。あ、あ！だめ、だめ。
Hold on. Ah, ah! No, no.
１周年配信でＢＡＮされたらどうするんですか！
What if I get banned on my 1st anniversary stream!
よいしょ。
Heave-ho.
ありがとうございました。あらら。
Thank you very much. Oh my.
よいしょ。
Heave-ho.
はーい。
Yes.
よかったね。ありがとうございます。えー、
That was good. Thank you. Um,
じゃあラミィもチャレンジしようと思うんですけど。
Well then, I'm thinking of trying the challenge too.
でもさ、やっぱラミィはどこに貼るっつーてさ。
But you know, for Lamy, where should we stick them?
どこ、ラミィってどこが一番揺れるのかな。
Where, for Lamy, where does it shake the most?
ちょっとジャンプ一回して。おしり？
Let me try jumping once. My butt?
いや、逆に、もう今までの全箇所に貼って、
No, on the contrary, let's stick them on all the previous spots,
どこが一番歩数計が回るのかっていうのを。
And see where the pedometer counts the most.
あき、ノエル先輩、マリン、団長でポンポンポン。
Aki, Noel-senpai, Marine, Danchou... one by one.
それぞれ自分が貼ってたところに貼ってあげよう。
Let's each stick them where we were wearing them.
おっけい、さあ。
Okay, let's go.
ついにラミィのケツに触れる日が来ました。
The day I finally get to touch Lamy's butt has come.
団長。
Danchou.
あ、ちっちゃいおしりですこと。
Ah, what a tiny little butt.
これ絵面大丈夫？ねえ。
Are the visuals for this okay? Seriously.
ラミィさ、下ケツと上ケツどっちがいい？
Lamy, do you prefer lower butt or upper butt?
上かな。
Upper, I guess.
上ケツ、こっち？ここら辺？
Upper butt, here? Around here?
でも、こっちの方がほぼ一緒かも。
But, this side might be almost the same.
じゃあ、やっぱ真ん中ケツにするね。
Then, I'll go with middle butt after all.
なんだろうこれ、すごい。
What is this, it's amazing.
これを０にリセットして。
Resetting this to zero.
おっけい、リセット完了と。
Okay, reset complete.
ついでにおしり触って。
And touching the butt while I'm at it.
おっけい。ちょっと時間が余ったからもう一回触って。
Okay. Since there's a little time left, I'll touch it again.
いいよ、いいよ。余ってないよ。
It's okay, it's okay. No, there isn't.
おっけい。はい、ありがとうございます。
Okay. Yes, thank you very much.
え、じゃあちょっと３人でスタートのあれをお願いします。
Eh, well then, could you three do the "start" thing?
じゃあラミィの振り振りチャレンジまで、
Then, for Lamy's Wiggle Challenge,
はい、用意、スタート！
Yes, ready, start!
行け、行け！楽しそう。
Go, go! Looks fun.
１周年を満喫している。
Enjoying the 1st anniversary.
ラミィ１周年で上がりまくってる。
Lamy's spirits are soaring for her 1st anniversary.
ラミィこんなに嬉しそうなラミィは。
I've never seen Lamy so happy.
生まれて初めて見ました。
In my whole life.
喜びバタバタ、ジタバタです。
A flurry of joy, a total fluster.
激しい、激しい。
Intense, intense.
ＢＧＭも思い出にこれを掛けたい。
I want to play this BGM for the memories too.
ガチじゃ。もうアイドルの姿をかなぐり捨てて。
For real. She's thrown away her idol persona.
激しいダンスを。
An intense dance.
すげー回ってるぞ。
It's counting like crazy.
ゲッターのごとく。終了ー！
Just like Getter. Finish!
はー、どこが一番揺れたんだろう。
Phew, I wonder where it shook the most.
見てみましょう。順番に見ていきますか。
Let's check. Shall we look one by one?
じゃあ一番ラミィが自信ないところどこ？
Then, where's the spot you have the least confidence in?
あ、そうだね。
Ah, that's right.
腰かな？
Waist, maybe?
もし？じゃあ、アキ先輩お願いします。
Pardon? Okay, Aki-senpai, please.
腰はですね、115回。
The waist is 115 counts.
おお、いいよ！いい感じよ！
Ooh, nice! Looking good!
じゃあ、お尻？
Then, how about the butt?
お尻はですね……お！117回！
The butt is... oh! 117 counts!
おおお！強い！
Oooh! Strong!
じゃあ、大胸筋は117回。
Then, the pecs are 117 counts.
あれ？一緒！一緒！
Huh? It's the same! The same!
ということは……なんだ？
Which means... what?
バランス型ということで。
That means I'm a balance type.
バランス型！すべてがバランスよく。
Balance type! Everything is well-balanced.
すべてを兼ね備えたラミィになったということかな？
Does that mean Lamy has it all now?
でもあれですね、総合結果……
But you know, the overall results...
ノエル先輩の大胸筋が一番強いということで！
Show that Noel-senpai's pecs are the strongest!
やったー！ウガハハイ！ヤー！
Yay! Wha-ha-ha! Yeah!
え、これなんかあるの？ご褒美とか。
Wait, is there a prize for this? Like a reward.
何もないです。
There's nothing.
あ、何もない。なんなんかい。
Oh, nothing. Then what was that for?
ただ、ラミィが見たかっただけです、これを。
I just wanted to see this.
何これ？
What is this?
やりたい放題だなぁ。えー、ということでね……
Doing whatever she wants! And so...
ポセイドン・フリフリでーす！
It's the Poseidon Shake-Shake!
なんだこれ。ちょっと……はい。
What's this? Wait... okay.
えー、ということでね。一旦これ剥がしますね。
Well, so, I'll take these off for now.
そうだね。剥がしてあげるよ！
Right. I'll help you take them off!
ラミィ、フリフリ触って。一旦、ペリペリ……
Lamy, shake-shake touch. First, peel peel...
お水も飲みたい。
I want to drink some water too.
お水ね。そうだね。いっぱい飲ませてあげる。
Water. Right. We'll give you plenty to drink.
おい！あ、やばいやばい……ビシ……ありがとうございます。
Hey! Ah, wait, wait... snap... thank you very much.
あ、お水も飲ませてあげる……剥がしかった……
Ah, I'll let you drink water too... it was hard to peel...
これラミィ、はいはいはい……はいはいチュチュ……
This, Lamy, yes yes yes... yes yes, sip sip...
はいはいチュチュして。はいはいチュチュ……
Yes yes, sip sip. Yes yes, sip sip...
うっとうしいな……はいラミィチュチュして。
How annoying... here Lamy, have a sip.
はいラミィチュチュして。チュチュさん。
Here Lamy, have a sip. Sip-san.
あ、あ……OK OK……
Ah, ah... OK OK...
はい、ということでね、それでは、続いてはね、視力……
Okay, and so, next, we have eyesight...
というか反射神経を！
Or rather, reflexes!
反射神経か！見ていきたいと思います！
Reflexes! Let's check them out!
心眼で叩いて被ってジャンケンポン！
Mind's Eye Hammer-Helmet Rock-Paper-Scissors!
心眼？心眼？
Mind's eye? Mind's eye?
どういうこと？心の目で見ろ！心の目！
What does that mean? Look with your heart! Your heart's eye!
あ、なるほど！なんか出てきたぞ！
Ah, I see! Something's come out!
あらあら……ということでね……すごい。
Oh my... And so... Amazing.
これね、今回お酒飲んでやったら面白いなと思ったんですけど……
I thought it would be fun to do this while drinking, but...
さすがにちょっと難しいので、素らふでほろ酔い気分を味わうために……
That's a bit difficult, so to get a tipsy feeling while sober...
目を瞑って……あ、そういうことね. なるほど。
We'll close our eyes... Ah, I see. Got it.
叩いて被ってジャンケンポンしていきたいなと思います。
I want to do the Hammer-Helmet game.
なるほどね……ということで、なんていうんだっけ？トーナメント制みたいな……
I see... So, what was it called? Like a tournament style...
やっていこうかなと思うんですが……
I'm thinking of doing that...
まずね、ちょっと一回見せましょうか、どんな感じでやるかってのを。
First, let's show you once how it's done.
お手本？そうですね、じゃあちょっとラミィに絶対的な自信が……
A demonstration? Yes, well, Lamy has absolute confidence...
勝てる自信があるという方！泣かす。
Those who are confident they can win! I'll make her cry.
泣かす！挑戦状！殺す……ころ……で……
I'll make her cry! A challenge! I'll kill... kill... okay...
じゃあね……あれ、逆でしたね。そうですね。OK OK OK。
Well then... Oh, it was the other way around. Right. OK OK OK.
じゃあね、ちょっとマリン先輩と一戦やりながらどんな感じになるかってのをね……
Then, I'll do a match with Marine-senpai to show you how it goes...
ちょっとイメトレして……こうね. OK OK OK. そうそうそうそう。
Doing some mental training... like this. OK OK OK. Yes, yes, yes.
ね？あ、逆逆逆……ええ、こうね。
See? Ah, reverse, reverse, reverse... yeah, like this.
よいよい！はいはいはい……ということでね、まずは普通にジャンケンポンってやるんですが……
Ready! Yes, yes, yes... So, first we do Rock-Paper-Scissors normally...
目は瞑ってやるので……はいはい. グーチョキパー何を出すかも口で言う。
Since we're doing it with eyes closed... yes, yes. We'll also say what we're throwing out loud.
口でね。そうそう. で……
Out loud. Right, right. And...
自分が勝ったの負けたなってのを瞬時に判断して……はいはいはい……
Instantly judge if you won or lost... yes, yes, yes...
こう被ったり……はいはいはい……逆だなこれ. 逆だね。
Put on the helmet like this... yes, yes, yes... It's the other way around. It is.
はいそうね……こうしたり……
Yes, right... Doing this...
叩いたり、見えないのでね……おい！ふざけんな！叩いてんじゃねーよ！
Hitting, since we can't see... Hey! Don't mess around! Don't hit me!
はい……やらねやらね……はい、やっていきたいと思います。
Yes... no no... Yes, let's do this.
じゃあこのまま第一戦行きましょうか. このまま行く？あー、まぁちょっとかかってこい。
Then let's go straight into the first match. Go like this? Well, come at me.
あんなラミィ負けないんで. いや、泣かす。
I won't lose. No, I'll make you cry.
じゃあラミィは超泣かす. もうかかってこいや！
Then I'll really make you cry. Just bring it on!
頑張れラミィ！勝てる気でいるのか！
Good luck Lamy! You think you can win?!
勝てる気しかいないわ！ということでそれでは行きます！
I can only see myself winning! So, here we go!
目閉じてね. そうです. 目瞑った. はい目瞑りました。
Close your eyes. Yes. Eyes closed. Yes, I've closed my eyes.
心眼で叩いて被ってジャンケンポン！はい！
Mind's Eye Hammer-Helmet Rock-Paper-Scissors! Yes!
せーの！最初……ね！揃えて揃えてください！
One, two! First... Hey! Please sync up!
ジャンケン？最初はグー？最初はグー？最初はグー……
Rock-Paper-Scissors? Start with rock? Start with rock? Start with rock...
え、始まってる？始まってる？待って待って一回。
Eh, has it started? Has it started? Wait, wait, one more time.
せーのでから行って. もう気が合わないなぁ。
Start from 'one, two'. We're not in sync at all.
合わせて合わせて. 最初はグー！
Sync up, sync up. Start with rock!
最初はグー！ジャンケンチョキ！アイコアイコ！
Start with rock! Rock-Paper-Scissors scissors! It's a draw, it's a draw!
アイコは大丈夫. 一回. OK。
Draws are fine. One more time. OK.
最初はグー！ジャンケンチョキ……何？なんて？パー！
Start with rock! Rock-Paper-Scissors scissors... what? What did you say? Paper!
（ハンマーを振り下ろす）
(Swings the hammer)
え、何で？待って. どこにある？ないんだけど！
Eh, why? Wait. Where is it? It's not here!
当たり！えー！
Hit! Eh!
机叩いてただけでしょ！完全に武器を失ったら勝つ手段ないよね。
You just hit the table! If you completely lose your weapon, there's no way to win.
あり得ないんだがマリン先輩！超適当にでもなくない？
Unbelievable, Marine-senpai! Wasn't that super appropriate though?
ちょっとちょっと待ってね. 今、今、今わかった. 今わかった。
Wait, wait a second. Now, now, I get it. I get it now.
今データ取得した. この机の物理演算今取得しました。
I just acquired the data. I've acquired the physics calculation of this table.
OK. データ取得完了. じゃあ次が本番ですかね。
OK. Data acquisition complete. Then is the next one for real?
OK OK OK. はい、行きますよ. 目瞑った。
OK OK OK. Yes, here we go. Eyes closed.
ちょっと待って. あん？左にあるハンマーが戦場のやつね。
Wait a minute. Huh? The hammer on the left is the one for the battle.
そうそうそう. これがこれで……OK OK OK. はい行きます！
Right, right, right. This is this... OK OK OK. Yes, here we go!
それではいきます。
Here we go.
最初はグー、ジャンケン、ポイ！
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
あいこで...
Draw...
最初はグー、ジャンケン、グー、チョキ！
Rock, paper, scissors, scissors!
あ、あ、あ...
Wait, wait...
はい、きかない。
It didn't work.
はい、きかないよ。
It didn't work at all.
もう一回かな？
One more time?
最初はグー、ジャンケン、パー！
Rock, paper, scissors, paper!
あー！
Aaah!
なんで、もう船長、もう何が起きてるんだ、今。
What the heck, Captain... what's even happening?
でもガードね。
But I blocked it.
なんでこれさ、ラミィがさ、叩くのめっちゃ遅いわ。
Why is it that Lamy's hitting is so slow?
え、ねえ、今ラミィのせいにしました？
Wait, did you just blame Lamy for that?
船長が勝ってさえ、ジャンケンで船長が勝ってさえいればこの試合終わる。
If the Captain just wins at Rock-Paper-Scissors, this match will end.
ジャンケンで船長が勝つだけ。
The Captain just needs to win Rock-Paper-Scissors.
いいですね、ね、もうこれ最後の勝負ですね。
Right, this will be the final round then.
最初はグー、ジャンケン、チョキ！
Rock, paper, scissors, scissors!
よわ！
So weak!
はい、これはラミィの勝ちではない！？
Wait, isn't this Lamy's victory!?
ラミィの勝ち！
Lamy wins!
WINNER 雪花ラミィ
WINNER: Yukihana Lamy
船長ジャンケン弱くないか？
Captain, aren't you really bad at Rock-Paper-Scissors?
お尻見えてるよ、お尻丸見えだよ。
Your butt is showing, it's totally visible.
それでは、次の勝負いきます。
Now then, let's move on to the next match.
行くぜ！
Let's go!
アキ先輩 vs ノエル先輩！
Aki-senpai vs. Noel-senpai!
おらー！マッスル対決じゃん。
Whoa! It's a muscle match.
本当だ、マッスル対決だ。
True, it's a battle of the muscles.
確かに、ムキムキ対決。
Indeed, a buff girl showdown.
パワーでどうにかする、なんならヘルメットを貫通させるまである。
I'll handle it with power. I might even punch through the helmet.
ヘルメット叩き割る。
I'll smash the helmet to pieces.
それは本当にいいことだね。
That sounds like a great idea.
それでは、よーい、スタート！
Alright, ready, start!
最初はグー、ジャンケン、チョキ！
Rock, paper, scissors, scissors!
あ、あいこ、あいこでパー！
Draw, draw, paper!
あいこ、あいこでパー！
お、うまい！うまいぞ！
Oh, nice! Great defense!
もう一戦！
One more match!
最初はグー、ジャンケン、チョキ！
Rock, paper, scissors, scissors!
あいこ、あいこでパー！
Draw, draw, paper!
早！反応マジで早！
Fast! Her reactions are seriously fast!
行くぞ！はい。
Here we go! Ready.
最初はグー、ジャンケン、チョキ！
Rock, paper, scissors, scissors!
あいこ、あいこでグー！
Draw, draw, rock!
あいこ、あいこでチョキ！
Draw, draw, scissors!
一生懸命今、5回くらいやって、割ろうとしたね今ね。
You were really going for it, trying to smash it like five times just now.
アキ先輩がうまいな、これ。
Aki-senpai is really good at this.
うん、やばい、髪の毛になんか引っ張られてる気がする。
Yeah, this is bad. I feel like something is pulling on my hair.
若干、これお互いちょっと実力の差がね。
There's a bit of a skill gap between them.
じゃあ次で、防衛ができたら。
Well then, in the next round, if someone successfully defends...
守れたらその人の勝ちにするか。
If you can block it, we'll make that person the winner.
そうしましょう、よしオッケー。
Let's do that. Alright, OK.
まずジャンケンに勝つことだ。
First, I need to win at Rock-Paper-Scissors.
最初は...あ、ちょっと待ってね。
First is... ah, wait a second.
少々、少々お待ちを。
Please wait just a moment.
ツインテールが今ちょっと荒ぶっちゃって、ちょっと待ってね。
My twintails are acting up right now, wait a sec.
あ、や、ツインテールもね、激しい戦いの末。
The twintails too, after such a fierce battle...
若干今いろんなものが荒ぶってる、異世界と更新してるのでね。
Various things are going wild. They're communicating with another world.
なに？ちょっと、わー、びっくりした。
What? Whoa, you startled me!
ついでに触ろうとする。
Trying to touch her while we're at it.
なにしてんですか、やめてくださいちょっと。
What are you doing? Please stop that.
はい、今直してますね。
Alright, she's fixing it now.
異世界と更新中。
Currently communicating with another world.
やばい、強くなってくる。
Watch out, she's getting stronger.
パワーアップしてる、まさかの直りました？
She's powering up. Oh, is it fixed now?
はい、いけそうです。
Yes, I'm ready to go.
それではこれが最終決戦となります。よし、行くぜ。
Alright, this will be the final showdown. Let's go.
お、緊張感が。
Oh, the tension...
無音だ、無音の時間が流れてる。
Silence. A moment of silence is passing.
なんならこれが優勝決定戦まである。
This might even be the championship match.
いや、違う。
No, it's not.
ラミィとの戦いを控えてるから。
Because I still have a match with Lamy waiting.
最初はグー、ジャンケン、チョキ！
Rock, paper, scissors, scissors!
あいこ、あいこでパー！
Draw, draw, paper!
あいこ、あいこでグー、チョキ！
Draw, draw, rock, scissors!
これは、アキ先輩の勝ち！
Aki-senpai is the winner!
イェーイ！やったー！強かったね。
Hooray! That was a strong performance.
WINNER アキ・ローゼンタール
WINNER: Aki Rosenthal
それではね、優勝決定戦に進む前に。
Now then, before we move on to the final match...
最弱王を決めたいなーと。
I'd like to decide the 'King of Weakness.'
なんだって？最弱王か。
What was that? The King of Weakness?
え、こやつと戦うのは、えー、最弱...
Having to fight this person... the weakest...
いやいやこっちこそ、さあ、並んで。
No, no, I'm the one who... come on, line up.
正式に、何ですか、この合法的にノエルを叩けるチャンスが来たな。
Formally, how should I put it? The chance to legally hit Noel has finally come.
そうですね、叩けるものならば。
Indeed, if you're even capable of hitting me.
泣くんじゃねえぞ。
Don't start crying on me.
さっきの戦いで何言ってんだか。やれやれ。
After that last match, look who's talking. Good grief.
3期生対決だね。最弱王決定戦ということでね。
It's a battle between 3rd Gen members, the match to decide the weakest.
用意、スタート！
Ready, start!
最初はグー、ジャンケン、チョキ！
Rock, paper, scissors, scissors!
あいこ、あいこでパー！
Draw, draw, paper!
はい、ノエル先輩の勝ちということで…
And so, Noel-senpai is the winner...
WINNER 白銀ノエル
WINNER Noel Shirogane
なんでー！
Why?!
最弱王はマリン先輩ということになります。
The king of the weakest is Marine-senpai.
弱、弱。
Weak, weak.
いや、弱い者いじめしちゃったな。
Man, I really bullied the weak.
それではですね、えー、勇者、あ、勝者決定戦ということで…
Now then, um, to decide the hero... I mean, the winner...
この中で一番強いのを決めたいと思います。
I'd like to decide who's the strongest among us.
あ、勝者決定戦、ラミィ vs アキ先輩！
The winner's battle, Lamy vs. Aki-senpai!
ハーフエルフ対決！
Half-elf showdown!
どっちがハーフエルフとして格が上か、見せつけてやんよ！
I'll show you which of us is the superior half-elf!
見せつけますよ、ハーフエルフ。
I'll show you too, as a half-elf.
ということで行きます。目瞑って。
Here we go then. Close your eyes.
最初はグー、ジャンケン、ポイ！
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
キレがあるわ。キレがあるね。
That was sharp. Very sharp.
最初はグー、ジャンケン、グー！
Rock, paper, scissors, rock!
強すぎたー。これアキロゼだ、アキロゼだこれ。
That was too strong. This is Akirose, true Akirose.
ハンマーが似合うな。
The hammer suits her.
WINNER アキ・ローゼンタール
WINNER Aki Rosenthal
Winner, アキ・ローゼンタール！
Winner, Aki Rosenthal!
10%くらいしか力出してなかったんですけどね。
I was only using about 10% of my power.
強すぎたー。もうナチュラルに強かった。
Too strong. She was just naturally strong.
えー、以上、叩いて被ってジャンケンポンでした。
Well, that's it for Rock-Paper-Scissors with a hammer and helmet.
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
なるほど、こちらも景品はないと。
I see, no prizes here either.
あ、何もないです。今日は。
Ah, nothing today.
ラミィさんがやりたいことをやるだけの配信なんで。
This is just a stream where Lamy does whatever she wants.
あ、そういうことです！配信なんで！
That's right! Because it's a stream!
えー、それではですね、ここまで色々やってまいりましたけれども…
Now then, we've done all sorts of things so far...
どうですか？ラミィの先輩たちへの思い、伝わってますか？
How is it? Have my feelings for my seniors reached you?
雑だなって思ってるよ。
I think it's been pretty rough.
何を伝えようとしてやってんの、これ？
What are you even trying to convey with this?
伝わってるって逆に…何を伝えたいのか今のところまで分かってない。
You say they've reached us, but... I haven't understood what you want to say at all yet.
何、何を伝えたくてやってんですか、これ？
What, what message are you trying to send with this?
まあまあまあ、最後にね、はい。
Well well well, at the end, yes.
なかったことにした、今。
She just ignored us.
え、最後にラミィから一番のお願いがあるんですよ。
Well, Lamy has one big final request.
それは、ラミィが、先輩たちからの、愛が欲しい！
That is, Lamy wants... love from her seniors!
求めちゃったよ、今度は。
She's actually asking for it now.
求めちゃってるねー。
She's really asking for it.
ということで、最後はラミィに愛をささやいて、プロポーズ選手権！
So, finally, whispering love to Lamy, it's the Propose Championship!
プロポーズ選手権
Propose Championship
もうね、今日はラミィの私利私欲。
Really, today is just Lamy's self-interest.
私利私欲すぎるね。
Too much self-interest.
ラミィがやりたいことやってきたわけなんですけれども…
I've been doing what I want to do, but...
せっかくね、こんな大好きな先輩たちに集まっていただいているので…
Since I have such beloved seniors gathered here...
先輩たちからの愛の言葉をいただきたいなー、なんて思っちゃったりとかしちゃってるんですよ。
I'm thinking I'd like to hear some words of love from my seniors.
ごり押しで進めてきた…
She pushed it through forcefully...
もう、有無を言わさなやん。
She won't take no for an answer.
話は聞かん！
I won't listen!
えー、ちょっとラミィに一人ずつプロポーズをしていただきたいなと思うんですけど…
I'd like each of you to propose to Lamy one by one...
誰からラミィにプロポーズをしてくれるかな？
Who's going to propose to Lamy first?
シーン…
*Silence*
なんでだよ！
Why is it silent?!
お、誰から行くんだっけ？
Oh, who's going first?
誰から行く…？
Who's going...?
マリンがやっぱトップバッターかな？
Marine should be the lead-off batter, right?
あ、最初だったっけ？
Oh, was I first?
え、ということで、じゃあマリン先輩から愛をささやいていただけるってことで、よろしいですかね？
So, Marine-senpai will be the one whispering love, is that okay?
しょうがないな、やってやるか！
Can't be helped, I'll do it!
お、言ったね、言ったね。
Oh, she said it, she said it.
じゃあ始めていきますか。
Then shall we begin?
何だこれは！
What is this?!
はい、外野どいて、はい、外野どいて。
Okay, spectators move aside, spectacles move aside.
ここ？ここなの？
Here? Is it here?
ここどこ？
Where is this?
よいしょ、よいしょ。ちょっと待って、今足直したから。
Heave-ho, heave-ho. Wait a sec, I just fixed my leg.
治療中。ちょ、ラミィ今さ、デートでさ、待ってる感じだして。
In treatment. Hey, Lamy, act like you're waiting on a date.
可愛い、可愛い。
Cute, cute.
お待たせ！はぁ、車に引かれちまってよ。
Sorry I'm late! Phew, I got hit by a car.
マリン、どういってよ。
Marine, what are you saying?
怖いってよ。
That's scary.
ラミィ、今日のデート楽しかったな。
Lamy, today's date was fun.
楽しかったねー。
It was fun.
見てごらん。すごい夜景だ。
Look. What a great night view.
え、きれい！」
Oh, beautiful!
あ、あれは！
Ah, that is...!
すごい夜景。この星の数ほど俺の愛はある。
Amazing night view. My love is as vast as the number of stars.
見てごらん、ラミィ。見てごらん。
Look, Lamy. Look.
もしかしてこれって…
Could this be...?
これは喜んでいる、これは喜んでいるラミィの…
This is a rejoicing... this is a rejoicing Lamy's...
何を見せられてるんだ…
What are we being shown...?
1周年記念グッズのB2タペストリー！
The 1st anniversary merch, B2 Tapestry!
ラミィ、これはどういう状況の時のラミィの顔かな？
Lamy, what kind of situation is Lamy's face in this?
これはね、プロポーズをしてもらってるラミィのタペストリー。
This is a tapestry of Lamy being proposed to.
この億千万の星の数よりも俺の愛は強い。
My love is stronger than these billions of stars.
ありがとうマリン、最高！
Thank you Marine, the best!
アディ。あ！
Adie. Ah!
えーということでね、はい。
So, well, yes.
こういうね、地獄が待っているわけなんですけれども。大丈夫ですか？
A hellish situation like this is waiting. Are you ready?
なんか、うっすら何かが見えた気がします。
I feel like I saw something vaguely.
まぶしいな、あれ。なんだろう。まぶしい。まぶしい。
That's dazzling. What is it? So bright. So bright.
まぶしい。何か見えた気がする。気のせい？
Dazzling. I feel like I saw something. Was it my imagination?
気のせい。
It's your imagination.
気のせいですね。じゃあ、こんな感じでやっていきたいなと思うんですけど。
It's just your imagination. So, I'd like to proceed like this.
いや、でもこれ地獄だな。
Wow, this really is hell.
アキ Rosenthal 先輩をこの後にちょっと連れて行くのは、ちょっと忍びないから... じゃあ、団長！
It's a bit hard to bring Aki Rosenthal-senpai into this next... So, Dancho!
団長も、いいぞ。
Dancho is fine too.
じゃあ、ちょっと... 団長も、こっちから、こっちからね。
Well then... Dancho, from here, from here.
行きますか。
Shall we go?
いやー、すごかったな。ドキドキしたわ。
Wow, that was amazing. My heart was pounding.
あ、素敵...
Ah, wonderful...
ここは... ラミィ、見て。
This place is... Lamy, look.
いや、すごいな。あれって天の川かな？ 綺麗だね。
Wow, it's amazing. Is that the Milky Way? It's beautiful.
綺麗。本当にすごい。
Beautiful. It's really amazing.
あっ、なんかラミィの髪の毛に似てるじゃないか、色が。
Ah, doesn't the color look like Lamy's hair?
団長ね...
Dancho...
なんか色が... 移動してきたみたい。なんか色がついてきたね。
It looks like the color... moved here. The color followed us.
団長、このやっぱ水色も綺麗だけど、すごい... なんか出てくるんだ。
Dancho, this light blue is beautiful too, but wow... something's coming out.
で、ラミィの何が好きかって、この長い、このエルフ耳めっちゃ... あれ？ ちょっと待って。
And, what I like about Lamy are these long elf ears... huh? Wait a minute.
エルフ耳？
Elf ears?
なんだなんだ？ あ！ フレア！ フレア！
What's going on? Ah! Flare! Flare!
ここの、この髪飾りもめちゃくちゃ可愛いな。ちょっと、いいか？
This hair ornament is also super cute. Hey, can I...?
ぶちっ！ あいたっ！
*Snap!* Ouch!
取るなよ、お前！
Don't take it, you!
おお、綺麗だな。え、これ、団長使っていいか？
Oh, it's beautiful. Hey, can Dancho use this?
え、キーホルダーにして使ってくれるの？
Eh, you'll use it as a keychain?
もちろん、だよ。嬉しいなあ。
Of course. I'm so happy.
ここにつけて。ありがとう。
Attached here. Thank you.
画面に出てるのは「雪の結晶キーホルダー」！
What's on the screen is the "Snow Crystal Keychain"!
なんだってー！
What?!
で、プロモーションの流れ的にこれ、大丈夫かな？
Wait, is this okay for the promotional flow?
これ、ステマ？ もしかして。
Is this stealth marketing? Perhaps.
いや、これをキーホルダーにして、みんな持ってるから。
No, because everyone will have this as a keychain.
あ、ありがとう。いつでも見てるからな。ずっと、ずっとラミィと一緒だよ。
Ah, thank you. I'll always be watching. I'll be with Lamy forever.
アディ。バイバイ。アディだね。
Adie. Bye-bye. Adie, right.
え、ということでね、はい。何だったの？
So, well, yes. What was that?
疲れたな、ちょっと。疲れたね、なんか。
I'm a bit tired. That was tiring.
え、えー、こんな感じで、ラスト、じゃあ大トリを...
E-, e-, and now for the grand finale...
何にも触れねーのかよ！ あれ、何にも触れ...
You're not going to mention anything?! You didn't even...
あ、ちょっと。ね。よかったよ、よかったよ。
Ah, wait. It was good, it was good.
メル、細かいことは気にするな。そうだな。おいで、おいで。
Mel, don't worry about the small details. Right. Come here, come here.
地獄だな、これ。地獄見守りたい隊。
This is hell. The Hell-Watching Squad.
でもエルフの耳でちょっと恨み持ってるから。やべーやべー。はあ...
But I'm holding a grudge about the elf ears. Oh no. Phew...
えー、ちょっと待って. これ、やるのか？
Wait a minute. Am I doing this?
なんか意味深。なんだ、この... なんか不穏だな、これ。
So meaningful. What is this...? This feels ominous.
壮大。なんだか、すごく壮大。
Grand. Somehow, it's very grand.
ドキドキ、ドキドキ。なんだ、死にかけてる。どうしたの？
Thump-thump, thump-thump. What, she's dying. What's wrong?
ラミィ...
Lamy...
アキ、どうしたの？
Aki, what's wrong?
ラミィ... 音声が聞こえないよ。
Lamy... I can't hear the audio.
ラミィ、大丈夫？ 音声が聞こえない。
Lamy, are you okay? I can't hear the audio.
音声が聞こえない。
I can't hear the audio.
ちょっと耳の調子が... うっ... あ、今調整中ということですね。
My ears are a bit... ugh... Ah, so it's being adjusted now.
ごめんよ、ちょっと君への愛が強すぎて、アボガド間違えた。
Sorry, my love for you was so strong that I mistook an avocado.
あ、アボガドだった。なるほど。
Ah, it was an avocado. I see.
ラミィ... うん。
Lamy... Yeah.
俺は、この3ヶ月間...
For these past three months...
3ヶ月間。
Three months.
君への愛を形にしたくて...
I wanted to give shape to my love for you...
朝から晩まで、汗水たらして働いたんだ。
From morning till night, I worked with sweat and tears.
えー？ 何これ、やっぱり。
Eh? What is this, after all?
君に、一生付けてもらいたい。そう、あれを君に捧げたくて...
I want you to wear it forever. Yes, I wanted to give that to you...
なになに？ 汗水流して頑張ったんだ。
What, what? I worked hard, sweating.
だから君に、これを...
So, to you, this...
受け取ってほしいんだ！
I want you to accept it!
あ、光が... これ、光ってるけど...
Ah, the light... This is glowing, but...
すごい光ってるけど。ちょうどいい感じに。
It's glowing a lot. In a just-right way.
スノーフラワー・エンゲージリング！
Snow Flower Engagement Ring!
これは、受け取ってくれるかい？
Will you accept this?
もちろんよ！
Of course!
ラミィ！ ありがとう、アキ！
Lamy! Thank you, Aki!
ラミィー！！
Lamy--!!
なんか全部持っていかれたよな。何これ。
Somehow, they stole the whole show. What is this?
なんだこの茶番は。
What a farce.
えーということでね、本当にありがとうございました。
So, thank you very much.
え、ちょっと待って。何だったのかな、これ。
Eh, wait a minute. What was that all about?
何だったのかと言われますとですね、そうですね、こちら！ ドン！
If you're wondering what that was... well, it's this! Boom!
なんか出てきた。うちら、いいように使われた？
Something appeared. Were we just used for this?
一周年記念グッズが、BOOTH にてこの後9時から発売開始されます！
1st Anniversary Goods will be available on BOOTH starting today at 9 PM!
え、こちらですね。グッズの、グッズの内容はですね...
Well, here they are. The contents of the goods are...
数量限定でですね、直筆メッセージ入りのものもございます。
There are also items with handwritten messages in limited quantities.
こちらフルセット。フルセットはですね、箔押しのサインが入ったポストカードになっております。
This is the full set. It includes a postcard with a foil-stamped autograph.
ということで、全部セットだと、あのプロポーズ後のアフタートークボイスというものも...
So, with the full set, there's also an after-talk voice from after the proposal...
なんだって！ そのために我々はプロポーズしたんだ！
What! So that's why we had to propose!
なるほど、使われたのか。そういうことか。スンスン、スンスン。
I see, we were used. So that's how it is. *Sniff sniff*
えー、じゃあちょっとね、一個ずつ具体的にお出ししたいと思います. ドン！
So, I'd like to show each item specifically. Boom!
こちら、リンユウ先生の描き下ろし、B2タペストリーでございます！
This is a B2 tapestry newly drawn by Rin Yu-sensei!
雪花ラミィ 活動一周年記念 8月12日 21時販売開始
Lamy Yukihana 1st Anniversary Celebration - Sales start August 12, 9:00 PM
フルセット購入特典 リンユウ先生描き下ろしポストカード 特典ボイス 「これからも一緒に」
Full Set Purchase Bonus: Postcard drawn by Rin Yu-sensei. Bonus voice: "Together from now on"
B2 タペストリー イラスト：リンユウ先生 素材：ポリエステル サイズ：B2サイズ
B2 Tapestry. Illustration: Rin Yu-sensei. Material: Polyester, Size: B2
うわー！かわいい！
Wow! So cute!
これはね、ちょっと後ほど紹介するんですが、
This is, well, I'll introduce it in more detail later...
おい、あのプロポーズボイスっていうのもありまして、
Actually, there's also a "propose voice" included.
その時のワンシーンを書いていただいております。
And this is a scene from that moment.
なるほどー。ほえー。
I see. Ohhh.
はい！そして、もう一つ、ドン！
Yes! And one more thing, ta-da!
こちらですね、さっきノエル先輩が引きちぎった...
This is the snow crystal keychain that Noel-senpai "ripped off" earlier.
おい！引きちぎってないぞ！
Hey! I didn't rip it!
髪飾りのこの雪の結晶、キーホルダーとなっております。
The snow crystal hair ornament keychain.
こちらね、あの、このケースも付いてます。
This also comes with a case.
ケースもおしゃれね！かわいい！
そうなんですよ。こちらもとってもおしゃれです。
Even the case is stylish! It's cute!
It is! It's very stylish too.
そして次、ドン！
And next, ta-da!
おお！すごいの出た！出たー！
Oh! Wow! This is it!
スノーフラワーエンゲージリング！
ラミィの指の薬指、7号サイズとなっております！
Snow Flower Engagement Ring!
It's size 7, for Lamy's ring finger.
なるほど、これラミィがつけるという...
そうです！なるほどなるほど。
I see, so this is for Lamy to wear?
Exactly. I see, I see.
ちなみにですね、これを首から下げられるネックレスチェーンも付いております。
By the way, it also comes with a necklace chain so you can hang it from your neck.
なるほど！いいー！
プラス、こちらのケースも付いております。
I see! Nice!
Plus, this case is also included.
いいなー。これ、サインが入ってるのかな？
Oh, it's nice. Does it have a signature on it?
そうなんです！箱の下の方にね、ちょっとラミィのサインも入っておりますので、
Yes! Lamy's signature is on the bottom of the box.
おー、おしゃれ。飾っても良し、付けても良しの、エンゲージリングとなっております。
How stylish. You can display it or wear it. It's an engagement ring.
すごーい！なるほど。じゃあラミィがプロポーズされた感じなのかな、さっきのボイスも？
Amazing! So Lamy got proposed to? Like in that voice?
そういうことになります！なるほどなるほどー。
いや、自然な導入だったなー。
Exactly! I see, I see.
That was a very natural introduction.
すごい。超自然だったな。自然だな。さすが。
Amazing. Truly natural. As expected.
はい、ということでね。皆さん、今日本当に、ラミィの私利私欲の1時間、本当にすみませんでした！
So, everyone, thank you so much for this hour of Lamy's self-indulgence. I'm sorry!
いやいや。何かラミィの1年間ね、やっぱり成長したなーって思う。
No, no. Lamy, it's been a year... I feel you've really grown.
先輩をこうやって...何か圧が...全然、そんなことないですよ！
To be able to handle seniors like this...
Whoa, the pressure... No, not at all!
何か強いな...いや、ラミィ成長したなと思って。ね、盛大なね、グッズの振りもね。
Lamy has grown... even pitching all these goods like this...
先輩使っちゃうのもね、成長したな...！
本当にすみませんでした！
Using seniors too... grown so much!
I'm really, really sorry!
いいんだよ、そこが。これからもね、ちょっと図々しく生きていきたいと思いますんで、
It's fine, that's what makes it good.
I want to continue living with some audacity,
これからもラミィと仲良くしていただいて...！
もちろんだよ！イエーイ！
so please keep being friends with Lamy!
Of course! Yay!
エモトモポーズ！イエーイ！
ついでだから触っちゃえ。何でだよ！
Emo-tomo pose! Yay!
Since I'm here, I'll touch you. Wait, why!?
すぐそばにいたから。
ということで、ちょっとお一人ずつ感想なんかを聞いていってもよろしいでしょうか。
Just because you were close.
Well then, can I ask for each of your impressions one by one?
じゃあ、アキ先輩。はい。いやー、いやはや。
First, Aki-senpai. Yes, yes, yes.
まさかラミィちゃんの1周年記念にね、呼んでもらえるとは思ってなかったんだけど。今日、お酒、
I never thought Lamy-chan would invite me for her 1st anniversary. Today, alcohol...
飲むのかなと思ってたんだけど、今日さ、やった企画をお酒飲んでやると思ったら、飲まなくて正解だったかもしれない。
I thought we'd be drinking, but seeing the activities we did today, not drinking was the right choice.
かなり激しかったな。激しかった。これでちょっと飲んでたらね、
It was quite intense. True. If we drank,
そうそう。ちょっとね、確かに一人ぐらい、二人ぐらい、もう半分ぐらいになってたかもしれん、逆に立ってる人数が。
one or two people, maybe half of us, would be down. Lamy-chan would be the only one standing.
本当だ、脱落していく。いや、でもすっごい楽しかったから。はい！
People would be dropping out. But it was really fun! Yes!
またね、こうやって次の年もをお祝いしたいし。あとね、お酒で楽しく飲むやつも、なかなかできなかったりもするんだけど、
I want to celebrate your next anniversary too. And drinking together, we haven't been able to much...
絶対にやろう！やりましょうやりましょう！本当におめでとう。これからも頑張ってね！
Let's definitely do it! Let's do it! Happy anniversary, and keep up the good work!
ありがとうございます！ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
じゃあ、マリン先輩。あ、じゃあね。成長もすごい楽しかったんだけど、やっぱりね、ラミィの夢を、
Next, Marine-senpai. Okay. The growth was fun to see, but Lamy's dream...
この前船長のチャンネルで叶えてあげたんだけど、まあ、あれってさ、叶ってるようで、若干叶ってない。
I fulfilled it on Marine's channel recently, but it felt somewhat unfulfilled.
どういうこと？だから、やっぱり生でさ、したいかなと思って。
What do you mean? I want to do it live (in 3D)!
まさか、まさか！じゃあちょっと、今日ちょうどいい、
No way... so, today is perfect?
いいよ、ラミィ。ほら、ピコピコハンマーもあるんで。手でやって、ラミィ、手でやって。
I have the squeaky hammer too... Lamy, do it with your hand. Use your hand.
せーの！ああっ！
Ready, set! *Thump*
はげー音だな！100点満点いただきました。ここ切り抜きでおねがいします。
That was a solid sound! 100 points! Please put this in a clip.
激しかった。ありがとうございました。ね、ラミィの本当の夢も叶ったということで、マリン先輩、ありがとうございました。
It was intense. Lamy's true dream came true. Marine-senpai, thank you.
ああ...ああ...ちょっと嬉しそうだね。いい顔してんね。今日一で幸せそうな顔してる。
Ahh... ahh... She looks happy. She's got a great look. Happiest face of the day.
じゃあ、最後にノエル先輩、いいでしょうか。
Finally, Noel-senpai, are you ready?
はい！いや、今日は1周年記念配信にお呼ばれして、本当にありがとうございました。楽しかったです！
Yes! Thank you so much for inviting me to your 1st anniversary stream. It was fun!
さっきね、ラミィ、先輩をこうやって使うようになって...って言ったけど、それにも理由があってね。
As for Lamy using her seniors now... there's a reason for that.
最初やっぱりラミィは、先輩に対して、自分なんかがコラボとかも誘えないよ、みたいな感じの、
In the beginning, Lamy felt like "I can't even invite seniors to collab"...
やっぱ結構長かった、その期間が長いのを感じてたから。でも、色々ね、まあお酒を飲み始めたりね、自分を出すようになって...
That period was quite long. But now, after drinking alcohol and showing her true self...
初めて、その先輩とも絡むようになって、
For the first time, she started interacting with her seniors,
すごいね、生き生きしたラミィが団長今大好きです！
and I really love how lively Lamy is now!
あぁ！ありがとうございまーす！
Aw! Thank you so much!
これからもね、この3人、あの、全然出しに使ってください。
Please feel free to use the three of us anytime in the future.
使ってよ！使ってよ！
Use us! Use us!
今日はね、なんか今までで一番楽しそうなラミィの声がしたよ。
Today, Lamy's voice sounded the happiest it's ever been.
これも記念だから！ラミィの！
This is also a celebration! For Lamy!
あれ切り抜いてほしい。
I want that part clipped.
あれ好きだった。
I loved that part.
すごかったこれ。
This was amazing.
面白かったよ、もう。
It was so funny.
いやもう、本当にラミィもね、今日ホント1周年っていうね、記念で、
Really, for Lamy as well, today's 1st anniversary celebration,
大好きな先輩3人をお呼びさせていただいてね、プレゼントまで要求し、
inviting my favorite seniors and even demanding presents,
ね、強欲すぎ。
Yeah, so greedy.
ね、あの、ラミィがやりたかった歩数計フリフリとかね、
doing things Lamy wanted to do, like shaking the pedometer,
とりあえずね、もう本当にラミィの欲望を叶える1時間、
basically, an hour of fulfilling Lamy's desires,
ホント付き合っていただき、本当にありがとうございました！
thank you all so much for going along with it!
いえーい！楽しかったよ！
Yay! It was fun!
これからもね、ちょっとお酒を飲んだり、
From now on, maybe we'll drink some alcohol,
コラボしたりとか、
do some collaborations,
ね、あの、歌を歌ったりとか。
and, you know, sing songs together.
あ、歌うんですか！
Oh, you're going to sing!
ついにラミィが、ちゃんと歌いますよ！
Finally, Lamy is going to sing properly!
おおー！嬉しい！
Ooh! We're so happy!
そのうち！
Someday soon!
ラ～ラ～ラ～♪
La la la~♪
マリン歌えますよのアピールがすごい。
Marine's "I can sing" appeal is intense.
ね、マリンともこないだ歌ったじゃないですか。
Right, we sang together the other day, Marine.
ね、歌ったね。
Yeah, we did.
あき先輩も、ね、ノエル先輩も、
Aki-senpai and Noel-senpai as well,
一緒に歌うとか、やれたらいいななんて思っておりますので、
I hope we can sing together sometime,
よろしくお願いします、今後とも！
so please keep supporting me from now on!
お願いしまーす！
Please look forward to it!
え、そしてですね、このあと、
And also, after this,
え、9時から、さきほどのBOOTHでグッズがオープン、
at 9:00, the goods will be available on BOOTH,
記念グッズがオープンして、
the anniversary goods will be open,
9時15分から、
and from 9:15,
え、ラミィのね、ねぽらぼ！
there's Lamy's... NePoLaBo!
あ、そうだ！
Oh, that's right!
ねぽらぼ4人での、何かの動画がですね、
a video featuring the four of us from NePoLaBo,
あれは一体何なんですか？
what in the world is that video?
プレミア公開となっておりますので！
it will be released as a premiere!
どんなんだろう。え、気になる！
I wonder what it is. Oh, I'm curious!
見に行かないと分かんないってことですね！
You have to go watch it to find out!
そうです、見に行っていただければと思います！9時15分からです！
Yes, I hope you'll go watch it! It starts at 9:15!
プレミア公開！
Premiere release!
ということで！それでは！皆さん！ありがとうございました！
And with that! Well then! Everyone! Thank you so much!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much!
2周年のラミィもよろしくお願いします！
Please support Lamy in her second year as well!
いえーい！
Yay!
え、それではさよーならー！
Well then, see you later!
適当に締めた！
She wrapped it up so casually!
適当すぎ！
Too casual!
ね、雑か！
Man, how messy!
まあいい、ラミィらしいじゃないか！
Well, it's very Lamy-like, isn't it!
ラミィ、なんかジャンプしてると、おっぱいすごい。
Lamy, when you jump, your chest is really something.
やめてホント、そればっかなんだから！
Stop it, really, that's all you talk about!
さよならー！
Goodbye!
ゆるい感じがいいね。
I like this relaxed vibe.